const quizData = {
  title: "Day 1: DEMO",
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Question based on Concept?",
      options: [
        "OPTION 1",
        "OPTION 2",
        "OPTION 3",
        "OPTION 4"
      ],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
       question: "Question based on Concept?",
         options: [
          "OPTION 1",
          "OPTION 2",
          "OPTION 3",
          "OPTION 4"
            ],
          answer: 3
    },
    {
      question: "Question based on Concept?",
      options: [
        "OPTION 1",
        "OPTION 2",
        "OPTION 3",
        "OPTION 4"
      ],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 4
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 3
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 1
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 3
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 4
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 4
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 2
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 3
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 1
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 4
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 1
},{
  question: "Question based on Concept?",
  options: [
    "OPTION 1",
    "OPTION 2",
    "OPTION 3",
    "OPTION 4"
  ],
  answer: 3
}
  ]
};
